{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the _____________ , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["mouse", "zoo", "tree", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["so", "sometime", "Sometime", "later"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lifted", "by", "him", "and"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["mouse", "search", "paw", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: of", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["a", "they", "of", "search"]}, {"explanation": "let is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and _____________ him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["let", "go", "help", "take"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["in", "search", "to", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["a", "later", "captured", "hunters"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: so", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["so", "his", "that", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tickled", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["mouse", "The", "that", "tickled"]}, {"explanation": "was is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion _____________ so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["was", "tied", "went", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["take", "let", "help", "go"]}, {"explanation": "zoo is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["paw", "wagon", "search", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in _____________ of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["zoo", "wagon", "tree", "search"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["a", "tree", "lion", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tied", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["hunters", "Sometime", "the", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["they", "the", "wagon", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "a", "zoo", "wagon"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: let", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["let", "The", "him", "idea"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went _____________ search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["that", "in", "of", "after"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: few", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["the", "few", "and", "tied"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: was", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["and", "was", "the", "to"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him _____________ he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["after", "of", "that", "in"]}], "success": 1}